Listen to the speakers and infer the relationships
Use the vocabulary to complete each statement listen again if necessary
Speaker 1
Well after a few years my brother finally got married again his new wife is really nice
She has three daughters and I know he loves them a lot
Speaker 2
Carol and I are very close to my dad when I was about 7 so we really grew up together
Speaker 3
My parents got divorced when I was only 3
Together
Speaker for
Leo's are great kid I'm really glad I married his mother the three of us are really happy together
Sticker 5
Hank and I have the same father my mom is his stepmother his mother
Is my father's ex-wife