Listen and infer the marital status of the person in each conversation
Circle the correct status
Conversation one
Who are these people in the picture that older couple those are my in-laws
Just Like Larry
Conversation to
These two are a cute couple who are they that's my aunt and that's her ex-husband
Ex husband yeah they're not married anymore
Conversation 3
Is that your sister yes it is her husband
That's her fiance
So nice
Conversation for
Who's that in this picture
That's my sister and her husband
Nice looking couple they were a nice looking couple they thinking about getting divorced
That's too bad yeah she's living with my parents right now