Read and listen to two women discussing family photos
Who's your brother
No that's my brother-in-law Matthew
He's married to my older sister Alexa
And this is their son Aiden
He's adopted
Do they have any other children
No just the one he's an only child
Looks like they're having a great time in New York
Actually they live there
They do
Wow
How often do you see them
We get together about twice a year
And what about these kids
They're my younger sisters
Ariana's the girl and these are her little brothers Cole and Casey
Cole and Casey look so much alike
Are they twins
They are
They all live in Vancouver but we keep in touch on the internet