Listen to infer
Now listen to each conversation again and complete each statement
Conversation one
Mr. Yuma's please call me Sarah Hart okay. Is that your nickname
I know it's my first name I don't have a nickname
Tell me what's your nationality actually I live in the capital Ankara but my hometown is
That's a really beautiful city on the Mediterranean Coast
I'm a computer programmer
Conversation to
Good evening
It's Keiko Nakamura
That's right but all my friends call me KK
So tell me Miss Nakamura what do you do
I'm a graphic designer actually and where are you from
Well I'm from Japan I live in Tokyo but I'm originally from Osaka
Conversation 3
We're talkin with
Pilar Rodriguez
That's right Pilar Pilar Rodriguez
No nickname Pilar
Okay
So you live in Uruguay right
I live there now in Montevideo but I'm actually from Buenos Aires in Argentina
And what are you doing Miss Rodriguez
I'm an interpreter I work for the Uruguayan government actually
Do you travel for your job
I do a lot I often go to Buenos Aires Brasilia Santiago Chile
Conversation for
So your name is Anthony Harris that's right but most people call me by my nickname Tony so it's Tony
Harris mr. Harris tell me what you do for a living
I'm a salesperson I work at a large electronic store in Chicago and United States so you're American
Actually no I'm from Toronto Canada but I've been in Chicago for over 10 years
That's right