Listen to the conversations conversation 1
Is that man over there David Egan
No that's George that's a very Dave's not here today
Really where is he from
He from Marseille in France
Conversation to
Who's that over there her name is Sonia Pereira what did she do they say she's an artist
She from around here know she's from South Paulo
So she's from Brazil
Conversation 3
Are you from around here
No I'm leaving Miami actually the name is Mark Mark zaleski
What do you do
I'm an interpreter I work for is BTW you're not from Miami originally though are you
As a matter of fact I was born and raised in Warsaw the capital of Poland
Conversation for
Is that Marjorie Baxter yes it is the new office assistant
That's right
Is it true she's from Australia
That's what I hear
Now listen again and write each person's occupation and nationality
Conversation one
Is that man over there David Egan
No that's George that's a very Dave's not here today
Really where is he from
He's from Marseille in France
Conversation to
Who's that over there are named Sonia Pereira what did she do they say she's an artist
She from around here she's from South Paulo
So she's from Brazil
Conversation 3
Are you from around here
No I leaving Miami actually the name is Mark Mark zaleski
What do you do
I'm an interpreter I work for is BTW you're not from Miami originally though are you
As a matter of fact I was born and raised in Warsaw the capital of Poland
Conversation for
Is that Marjorie Baxter yes it is the new office assistant
That's right
Is it true she's from Australia
That's what I hear