Listen for details listen to the conversations match the event and the place
Conversation one
Are you free on Sunday at 11:30 Nick Hornby is going to be at the city nights bookstore
Nick Hornby I love his books
What's he doing there
Giving a talk about his novel slam want to go absolutely
Conversation two
What's playing at the cinema center there's an old Marilyn Monroe movies showing at 7:10.
Not really I'm not a Marilyn Monroe fan
Conversation 3
Agamemnon is at the theater in the circle
What type of ...?
Famous Greek play
This performance tonight. If you want to go
Maybe
Conversation four
I'm in the mood for a good concert
What's playing at the festival
The Boston Symphony Orchestra Beethoven's 5th tonight. Sounds great
What time?
at 7:45. Let's do it
Well
It's at 6:30 now
Meet you there in an hour