Listen to the conversations about places
Write the number of each place in a box on the map
Be careful
There are three places
But seven boxes
Conversation one
Excuse me I'm looking for the city center do you know what that is
The city center let me sink
Usher go straight down the street
This right
Then turn right on Atlantic right on Atlantic
Dan go to the corner of Indian and Atlantic
The city center is on the right side of the street
You can't miss it
Thanks
Conversation to
Excuse me I'm looking for the art museum
Actually I'm not from around here
But I think that's it right across the street
All right I see it now thanks
Conversation 3
Mam excuse me
I'm looking for the Cluny feeder at any theater do you know the address
600 Hudson Street
Oh yeah I know where that is
Walk straight down Bay one block
Then turn left on Adriatic
Walk to the corner of Hudson and turn left
It's right there on the corner