Look at the map of the Entertainment District of Kingston
Listen again and write the number of each place and its location on the map
Be careful
There are five places but 10 boxes
Conversation one
Culture Fest this is Amy
Hello
Can you tell me where the classic film series playing at the Lamont theater
Do you know where that is
Actually
Could you give me the address and directions
1175 66th Street
Between Central Avenue and Greenway
Thanks
Zmovies I'll start at 7 right
And one more question
What's playing tonight
Tonight
Pets mee6
You're in luck tonight there's a double feature
Nice to meet you and the 39 steps
Two movies for the price of one
$10
Conversation to
Good morning Kingston culture Fest this is Amy may I help you
Yes thanks I'm interested in the history of Latin music lecture and concert on May 11th
That's at the Natural History Museum isn't it
Yes that's right 110 Greenway right across the street from Green Park
In the large Auditorium
Are there still some seats available
Let me check
Yes I have some seats available for the matinee
Would you like Orchestra or balcony
What's the difference in price
If you just give me your name you can pick them up at the Museum box office a half hour before the talk
Jeffrey
That's great
I thought that would be really expensive
In that case I think your cash receipts
Receipts will be in row e seats 10 and 11
10 + 11
Yes that's right
My name is David Duke low
And what time is the matinee
Conversation 3
Good evening this is the Kingston culture Fest box office how can I help you hello
I need two tickets to the Ludacris hip-hop concert
Which day
Friday the 10th please
That's shows at 7:30 right
We have orchestra seats at $25 and balcony seats at 18
Which would you prefer
I'll take the balcony
Are they good seats
Yes those are front row in the center seats 201 and 202
I think you'll be very happy with them rate
By the way just to be sure
What's the address
3600 Central Avenue across from the park
I'm confused green talk
Lemont Park I know what that is
Between 71st and 72nd
No you're thinking of the sports complex the Kingston concert hall is on the corner of West way
Thanks let me give you my name
Conversation for
Culturefest can I help you yes I need two tickets to The Lion King
I just love that play classic
Which day would you like to see it
Saturday the 11th
I'm sorry Saturday sold out
What about Sunday
Okay
Is that playing at the Longmont theater
Where exactly is gallery to
On Sunday the shows a matinee it starts at 2:30
All seats are $50
Conversation 5
Hello culture Fest
Hi I'd like to order tickets for the Picasso lecture
Which date please Thursday if that's possible and
How much are the tickets
Etsy
Yes I got space on Thursday all seats are $36
If we just confirmed the time that's at 8:30 correct
Actually it's at 8 on Thursdays and the lecture is at Kingston Gallery 2
Gallery one
That's on Greenway across from the Natural History Museum
Between 70th and 71st
Great