Listen to the conversations about entertainment and cultural events
Complete the chart with the kind of event and the time of the event
Conversation one
I feel like some loud music tonight how about some rock there's a great concert at PSA
Who's playing
Rock around the block
Oh yeah
What time is the show
You know on second thought that's past my bedtime tomorrow
Conversation to
Hey there's a reception of the Clark Street Gallery for their new exhibit
Really Who's the artist Martin you
Watching you I love his flower photos what do you think
What time is the reception from 7 to 9
Conversation 3
What are you doing tonight nothing much
Extra ticket to Twelfth Night
Twelfth Night is not a play by Shakespeare
Yep
Sounds like fun what time
At the Stage Theater
Great
I'll meet you there in front of the box office