Look at the chart and listen again
Circle the event if the person accepts the invitation
Conversation one
I feel like some loud music tonight
How about some rock there's a great concert at pfx
Who's playing
Rock around the block
Oh yeah what time is the show
On second thought that's tomorrow
Conversation to
Hey there's a reception of the Clark Street Gallery for their new exhibit
Really Who's the artist
Martin you I love his flower photos
What you think
What time is the reception from 7 to 9
Conversation 3
What are you doing tonight
Extra ticket to Twelfth Night
Twelfth Night
It's not a play by Shakespeare
Sounds like fun what time at the Stage Theater
Box office